We have to walk again?
(水月)
また歩くのか… もうヘトヘトだよ。
I'm exhausted.
(香燐)ヘッ… これから
北アジトに行くっていうのに➡
Humph... We're going to
the northern hideout now.
そんなんじゃ
着いたとたんに殺されちまうぞ。
At this rate, you'll be killed
the moment we get there.
(水月)
ボクは地図でしか知らないけど➡
I only know it through maps...
but is the place really that bad?
そんなに やばいとこなんだ？
北アジトは ただのアジトじゃない。
The northern hideout
is no ordinary hideout.
あそこは 人体実験場だ。
That place...
is where human experiments
are conducted.
そして そこで生み出された➡
And the unmanageable monsters that
result are kept locked up there.
手のつけられないバケモノばかりが
収容されてる。
(重吾)男… いや… やっぱり女…。
A male...
No, a female.
次に殺すのは やっぱり男だ。
No, I'll kill a male next, after all.
(重吾)
そうか… もう始めやがったか。
I see.
It's already begun...
どうして… どうしてお前は
死んじまったんだよ。
Why... Why did you have to die?
(ナルト)ふぁ～い。
RAMEN
That's pretty heavy food
to have in the morning.
(サクラ)寝起きから
ヘビーなもん食ってんな アンタ…。
サクラちゃん
今日は休日だってばよ。
Sakura, today's our day off.
How come you're up so early?
こんな朝早くから何？
もう お昼だよ。
It's already noon.
まぁ いいや。
Well, never mind.
すぐに顔洗って着替えてきて。
Just wash up quickly and get dressed.
I'll be waiting.
待ってるから。
なに!? デート？
Huh? Is it a date?
Idiot! Lady Tsunade has summoned us!
バカ！ 綱手様が呼んでんのよ！
ねぇ 疲れただろ？
少し休憩にしないか？
Say, aren't you tired?
How about a short break?
You're already taking a break!
つ～か
もう休んでんじゃねえか！
You are so hopeless!
ったく だらしないヤツだな。
北アジトまで まだまだだぞ。
We've still got a ways to go 'til
we get to the northern hideout!
キミとは行き先が違うんだ。
My destination is different
from yours.
ボクの心配は結構。 もう行ってくれ。
No need to bother with me.
Just go on ahead.
I remembered that I too have business
at the northern hideout!
ウチも北アジトに
用があるのを思い出した！
So I'm going to take care of that first!
そっちを
先に行くことにしたんだよ！
チッ！
((重吾 : うおぉ～っ！
Move...!
どけ～っ！ 殺すぞ テメエも！
I'll kill you too!
(君麻呂)やめろ 重吾。
Stop it, Jugo...
もう… いい。
That's...
enough.
お前は１人じゃない。
You're not alone.
(ボクがついてる))
You have me.
お前がいないんじゃ➡
Without you...
I can never leave this place...
オレはもう
一生ここからは出られない。
水月…
なんでアンタは サスケについてくる？
Suigetsu...
Why do you follow Sasuke?
I have a goal.
ボクには目的がある。
サスケといると それが叶うからさ。
And if I stick with Sasuke,
I can fulfill that goal.
Say, I should be asking you
the same question... Really.
ていうか そりゃ
こっちのセリフだよね～ ホント。
アンタたちの
目的が何かは知らないけど➡
I don't know what your goals are...
But you want me to join your team
despite knowing about Jugo?
重吾のことを知ってて
仲間にするって言ってんのか？
少しはね…。 一度
手合わせさせられたこともあるよ。
I know him a little.
We fought each other once.
He had an unusual ability
and was quite formidable.
おもしろい能力を使うヤツで
かなり強かったけど…。
But I couldn't figure out
what he was thinking,
何考えてるかわからない感じで
好きにはなれなかったけどね。
and I didn't really like him.
I understand he  sought out
Orochimaru.
自分から
大蛇丸に捕まりに来たらしいし➡
頭が どうかしてる。
He's got to be crazy.
According to rumors,
ウワサじゃ重吾は➡
Jugo usually has that
unusual impulse well under control.
ふだん その異常な衝動を
抑え込んでるらしいけど➡
But when he loses it,
he transforms into a ruthless killer.
キレたら恐るべき殺人鬼へと
性格も見た目も変貌するって話だ。
His personality and appearance
change completely.
へぇ～。 要は人殺しが大好きな
イカレ野郎ってことだろう？
In other words, he's a maniac
who loves to kill people.
But to Orochimaru,
Jugo's ability was enticing.
それでも 大蛇丸にとって
重吾の能力は魅力的だった。
大蛇丸は重吾の体液から➡
He invented an enzyme,
based on Jugo's body fluids,
which induced the same condition
in other Shinobi.
他の忍にも同じ状態を引き起こす
酵素を開発したんだからね。
アンタたちも知ってるだろう？
You guys know it too, right?
それが… 呪印だよ。
That's...the Curse Mark.
重吾は その唯一のオリジナルだ。
Jugo is the one and only
original carrier.
オレは ここから出る！
ジャマをするヤツは殺す！
I'm getting out of here!
I'll kill anyone who tries to stop me!
次は どいつだ!?
Who's...next?
Jugo of the Northern Hideout
(綱手)遅い！
何をチンタラしてた!? ったく！
You're late!
What took you two so long?! Cripes!
す… すみません！
I-I'm sorry.
ナルトのヤツが朝食という名の
お昼を食べてまして…。
Naruto was eating lunch,
which he calls breakfast...
(自来也)まぁまぁ 綱手。
Now now... Tsunade...
あれ？
エロ仙人 帰ってきてたのかよ。
Huh? Pervy Sage?! You're back!
久しぶりだのぉ ナルト！
It's been awhile, eh, Naruto?
なんだよ！ 帰ってきてたんなら
教えてくれりゃあ…。
Aw man! Why didn't you tell me
you were back?
あれから大変だったんだぞ。
(自来也)そうらしいのぉ。
We had a hard time after you left.
So I hear.
大方の話は聞いておるが
大活躍だったようだのぉ。
I got the gist of it, but I understand
you played a big part.
That's for sure.
あぁ そうなんだ。
オレってば ついに➡
I finally got my Collaboration Jutsu
to work in sync with the two toads.
ガマたちとのコラボ忍術を
完成させたぜ！
おぉ そうか そうか！
ついにやったか！
Oh, is that so?! You finally did it!
どうだ？ 新術 見てえだろ？
おぉ せっかくだし。
How about it?
Wanna see my new Jutsu?
Well, since I'm here...
I don't mind if I do.
見てみたいのぉ。
だろ？ だろ？
I knew it!
で そのあとはもちろん 一楽で
ミソチャーシューで決まりだってばよぉ。
And naturally, after that,
we'll go eat ramen at Ichiraku!
おぉ おごってやるとも！
お～！ 行こうぜ行こうぜ！
Sure, it'll be my treat.
- All right! Let's get going!
- Let's go! Your new Jutsu, eh...?
よ～し 行こう行こう。
新術かぁ 楽しみだ。
- I'm looking forward to this...
- Hey!!
(綱手/サクラ)ごらぁ！
だぁ～！
(自来也)お～。
- Ow!
- Oh!
ねぇ… 少し休まない？
Say, can we rest a bit?
水月 テメエ休んでばっかじゃねえか。
もうアジトだぞ！
Suigetsu! You keep stopping to rest!
We're almost at the hideout!
その刀か！ その刀が重いのか!?
Is it the sword?
Is it too heavy for you?
それ 置いてけこら～！
Then leave it, damn it!
サスケも なんとか言えよ！ ん？
Tell him, Sasuke!
どうした？
What's wrong?
(サスケ)見張り小屋のヤツは どこだ？
え？
Where's the guy who's on watch?
Huh?
あ… ホントだ おかしいね。
You're right... That's strange.
おい。
Hey...
北アジトの男だ。 まだ息がある。
He's from the northern hideout.
He's still breathing.
何があった？
What happened?
お… お前は うちはサスケか…。
Y-You're...Sasuke Uchiha...
助けてくれ…。
Help me...
どうしたんだ？
What happened?
大蛇丸が
死んだという情報から始まった。
I-It all started...
with the rumors that
Orochimaru was dead.
囚人たちが暴れだし➡
The prisoners went wild...
このままじゃ… うっ！
At this rate...
あららら 死んじゃった。
Oh dear... He died.
お前は たしか…。
You're...
なんなの あれ。
What is that?
呪印状態２だ。
すでに変化してやがる。
He's already in the
"Curse Mark Second State."
北アジトは そこだ。
さっさと重吾に会いにいくぞ。
The northern hideout is over there.
Let's go and see Jugo.
あ… おい！ 待て サスケ！
Huh? Hey! Wait, Sasuke!
あれ？ 誰なの？ これ。
Huh? Who is this guy?
男…。
次に殺すのは やっぱり男だ。
A male...
The next one I kill
will be a guy, after all...
よし 決めた。
All right, decided.
次に その扉から入ってきたヤツが
女だったら➡
If the next one who comes
through that door is a woman,
殺すことにしよう。
I'll kill her.
看守は全滅だな。
全員 脱獄しちまってる。
The guards have all been killed...
and the prisoners have escaped.
あれじゃ どれが重吾か
わかんないね… サスケ。
Then there's no way
we can tell which one is Jugo...
Eh, Sasuke?
香燐 アイツらの中に重吾はいるか？
Karin, is Jugo among them?
Cripes, what a pain!
Just wait a bit!
ったく うるさいな！
少し待ってろ！
Nope, he's not.
(香燐)フン… いないな。
(水月)なら おかまいなしってヤツで
オーケーだね。
Well then, I can fight without
worrying who they are.
急所は はずしておけ。
Just avoid killing them.
ハァ～ やっぱキミは
木ノ葉出身だなぁ。
You're from the Hidden Leaf,
after all...
You should've killed that
guy back there too, you know.
さっきの男も
殺せばよかったのに。
So naïve...
甘いね。
いくぞ。
Let's go.
うわっ！
うぉ～っ！
Stay away! You all stink!
寄るな！ 汗くせえ！
つええ… お前は…。
You're strong... You're...
フゥ～。
鍵だ。 見つけたぞ。
The keys!
I found them!
(重吾)殺す… 殺す！
Kill...
香燐 どっちだ？ 案内しろ。
Karin, which way?
Lead the way.
サスケ アンタ さっきから
なに仕切ってんだ！
Sasuke!
Why're you ordering me around, huh?!
いいから
早く調べてくれないかな。
Can you just hurry and check?
それがキミ ご自慢の能力だろ。
That's the ability you
pride yourself on, right?
あっちだ。
That way!
フゥ～…。
なんだ？
What is it?
Actually, it's this way.
ホントは こっちだ。
さぁ 行くぞ サスケ。
Let's go, Sasuke!
なぜ ウソをつく？
水月は あっちに…。
Why did you lie? Suigetsu went...
Suigetsu has a big mouth,
that's why I don't like him.
うるさいから 水月は嫌いだ。
行くぞ！
離せ 自分で歩く。
Let's go!
Let go... I can walk on my own.
しかし 呪印ってのは➡
So...the Curse Mark really does transform
the body into such an ugly shape...
体型を あそこまで
ブサイクに変化させるんだね。
サスケ キミも 呪印で
あんなふうになるのかい？
Sasuke, does your Curse Mark
do the same to you?
サスケ？ ボクの話をちゃんと…。
Sasuke... Are you listening...?
That witch...!
あの女…！
女だ… 女が入ってきたら… 殺す。
A woman...
If a woman enters,
I'll kill her...!
ここか。
あぁ 重吾は 中にいる。
Here?
Yeah, Jugo's inside.
来たな。
There...
Now then, which will it be?
さあ どっちだ？
よし。 じゃあ開けるぞ。
All right! I'm gonna open it!
I'll go in first. Karin, stay back.
オレが先に入る。
香燐 お前は下がってろ。
S-Sure!
お おう。
いや…。
No...
やっぱり男だ。
男が入ってきたら殺そう。
It's gotta be a guy.
If it's a guy, I'll kill him.
Bingo! I'm gonna kill!
ビンゴ！ 殺す！
He's coming!
来た！
おらぁ～！
あれ？ 戻ってきちゃったな。
Huh? I'm back where I started.
やっぱり あそこを右か。
I should've turned right back there.
クソッ あの女。
Damn that witch!
Y-You guys...
お前ら…。
Just what is your purpose
in coming here?
お前らはいったい
何が目的でここへ来た？
重吾を連れ出しにきただけだけど。
We came to take Jugo outta here,
so that he can join our team.
仲間にしたくてね。
Do you guys realize...
what you're doing?
お前ら 自分たちが
なにをしようとしてんのか➡
わかってんのか？
あんなヤツを この世に放したら…。
If you let that guy...
out into the world...
ボクも同感。
けど ボクが言い聞かせるさ。
I totally agree.
But I'll convince him...
with force, if necessary.
なんなら力ずくでね。
強いといっても アンタ程度じゃ…。
You may be strong, but you're hardly...
Listen... If it weren't for Sasuke's words,
you'd be dead right now.
キミ サスケの言葉がなけりゃ
今 死んでたとこだよ。
テメエらなんか 重吾に殺されちまえ。
Jugo will kill you all!
一人くらい かまいやしないか。
I really could care less
if one person died.
Sasuke!
サスケ！
ゲハハッ！
アハハッ。 ハァ。
すみません。 ナルトのヤツが
毎度まいど騒がしくって。
I-I'm so sorry!
Naruto always gets so rowdy...
こら バカナルト！
イテッ！
アンタも謝んなさいよ。
Hey, Naruto, you idiot!
Say you're sorry too!!
サクラちゃん 痛いってばよ。
Oww... Sakura that hurt!
And? What did you want
to talk about?
で なんなんですか 話って？
Huh? Mmm...
ん？ うむ…。
What's wrong, Granny Tsunade?
どうしたんだよ
綱手のばあちゃん。
Don't you have something
to talk about?
なんか話があるんじゃねえの？
そうだな。
Well...
There's certain information that is
being spread throughout the region...
実は 各地いたるところで
ある情報が流れていてな。
そのことについてだ。
情報？
It's about that.
Information?
なに？ なんだってばよ？
What? What about?
Orochimaru is dead.
大蛇丸が死んだ。
どうやら
うちはサスケがやったらしい。
It seems Sasuke Uchiha killed him.
そ… それって… ホントか!?
Is...
Is that...true?
まず間違いない…。
There's no mistake about it.
I heard it from a reliable source.
確かな情報スジから
聞いたからのぉ…。
Then...
じゃあ もう…。
アハッハッハ！ アイツが大蛇丸なんかに
やられるはずがねえってばよ！
Heh! After all, there's no way
he'd get killed by Orochimaru!
That means Sasuke will be coming back
to the Hidden Leaf! Right?
じゃあ サスケのヤツ
木ノ葉に帰ってくんだよな！
なぁ!?
That doesn't seem to be the case...
どうやら そうではないらしい…。
えっ…。
ゲハハハハ！
クッ…。
It's not over yet!
まだだ！
クッ！
Sasuke's Chakra...
《サスケのチャクラが…》
変化した…。
...changed!
ゲハハハ… また オレのコピー野郎か!?
Not another copy of me...!
ハッハッハッハ！
《サスケ…》
Sasuke...
But you're quite a guy
しかし 部分変化ができるとは
たいした野郎だぜ！
to be able to do
a Partial Transformation!
You're good at controlling
your Curse Mark!
呪印を扱うのが うめえな！
争う気はない。
I have no intention of fighting.
お前に話があるだけだ 重吾。
I only wish to talk to you, Jugo.
But you're quite a guy!
You're good at controlling
your Curse Mark!
ヘヘ… ヤマト隊長からもらった福引券。
I have no intention of fighting.
I only wish to talk to you.
狙うは もちろん１等！
カップラーメン １年分だ！
おっ ここだ！
Talk?
Jugo, I'm getting you out of here.
(いの)いらっしゃ…
って なんだ ナルトか。
なんだじゃねえだろ！
ところで オレのカップメン まだある？
Are you an idiot?!
You don't know anything!
オレのかどうかは 運次第ね。
What do you mean?
けど まだ出てないわよ １等！
よっしゃ～！
はい じゃあ３回ね。
頼むぞ ラーメン！
(いの)残念！
はい ハズレのアメちゃん。
クッソ～ 次こそ！
(いの)ハズレ！
はい アメちゃん パート２！
最後の１回に すべてをかける！
おらぁ～!!
(２人)あ！
大当たり～！
やった～！
はい！
特賞の自来也先生サイン入り➡
『イチャイチャタクティクス』３冊セット！
え～!? そんなのいるか！
アホらしい 帰ろ 帰ろ。
(カカシ)あれ？ 特賞出ちゃったの？
せっかく
福引券集めたのに… ショック。
(ナツ)『FAIRY TAIL』 前回までは…。
(ハッピー)ついに始まった➡
Ｓ級魔導士昇格試験！
第１次試験は
バトルもあるルートを選んで➡
勝ち進まなくちゃ
いけないんだけど➡
ナツの相手は いきなりギルダーツ！
まぁ 苦戦したけど
手加減してやったからなぁ。
(ハッピー)すごい強がり…。